[

  {
    "question": "What was the name of the Ravager that killed Jimmy in Limited Life?",
    "answers": ["Grian", "Sunday Driver", "Bad Boys Big Bad Dog", "The Curse", "Boogeyman"],
    "correct_answer_index": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "In Third Life, Scar used a clock to convince Bdubs to eliminate Impulse. Where did he get it?",
    "answers": ["Found it in a chest", "Cleo gave it to him", "He crafted it himself", "Bdubs dropped it", "Impulse dropped it"],
    "correct_answer_index": 4
  },

  {
    "question": "What was the color of Skizz's underwear in Limited Life?",
    "answers": ["Red", "Yellow", "Green", "White with hearts"],
    "correct_answer_index": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "How was the Double Life Warden killed?",
    "answers": ["Bow and arrow", "Fishing rod", "Sword", "Axe"],
    "correct_answer_index": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Who killed the Ender Dragon in Secret Life?",
    "answers": ["Scott", "Impulse", "Pearl", "Bdubs"],
    "correct_answer_index": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "BigB has an alternate ego that he uses throughout the series. What is his name? ",
    "answers": ["Cherry", "Berry", "Terry", "Jerry"],
    "correct_answer_index": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one of these hasn't been a feature in Bdubs' skin during the Life Series?",
    "answers": ["A golden tooth", "A red bandana", "A black eye", "A missing tooth"],
    "correct_answer_index": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "In Third Life, how did Martyn kill Ren to turn him red?",
    "answers": ["With an axe", "With TNT", "With a sword", "Shoved him off a cliff"],
    "correct_answer_index": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won \"You Bet Your Life\" in Last Life?",
    "answers": ["Cleo", "Scott", "Joel", "Lizzie"],
    "correct_answer_index": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which players weren't pressent for the trapdoor sleepover in Secret Life?",
    "answers": ["Martyn and Etho", "Etho and Tango", "Grian and Etho", "Martyn and Grian"],
    "correct_answer_index": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Scar and Pearl use to hurt their soulmates in Double Life?",
    "answers": ["Lava", "Gravel/sand", "Powdered snow", "Drowning"],
    "correct_answer_index": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was referred to as the \"Red King\" in Third Life?",
    "answers": ["Martyn", "Scar", "Ren", "Bdubs"],
    "correct_answer_index": 2
  }
]